DIXON GILLETTE: All right.
To begin laying single track, you're going to want to start out at your city that you are over.
Now, one thing that's important to keep in mind when laying track is you can only build track off of existing track.
You can't just start track out in the middle of nowhere.
To begin, you're going to want to select your Single Track icon here or push T on your keyboard.
What this will do is this will change your mouse pointer into your track selector.
And when you're not over your track, you will see a red circle with an X there.
That means you cannot lay track at that other position.
To change this into the green circle that you want, you bring it over the edge of your track and as you can see are mouse pointer changed.
To begin laying the track, you're going to left-click your mouse and simply drag your track towards the direction that you want to build in.
So we're going to go over here to the cornfields and build our track there.
To actually build the track, you're going to left-click again.
And as you can see, the track is actually built now.
Now, as you could see, if you keep dragging your mouse out you're still in Track Laying mode.
So you're going to want to exit your Track Laying mode by right-clicking on your mouse.
Now, one thing that's important to keep in mind is that when you are laying track, you're going to want to make sure that you have brought your track all the way within the green circle of the industry or city.
If you don't bring it within this transparent green circle, you're going to find that you won't be able to build a depot there, so make sure that you always bring it within the green circle.
And those are the basics of laying single track.